#### Contact

+254722161224 (Mobile) robleygori@live.com

www.linkedin.com/in/robleygori (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Python JavaScript MySQL

### Certifications

Scrum Fundamentals Certified

# Robley Gori

Software Engineer at Safaricom PLC Kenya

## Summary

A software developer driven by passion, excellence and the belief that the future will be written in code.

I enjoy being challenged and engaging with projects and technologies that require me to work outside my comfort-zone and knowledge set, as continuing to learn and overcome challenges fuel my growth. I am passionate about big data and analytics.

I am skilled & experienced in Python, Elixir JavaScript, Java, Docker, Microservices and DevOps.

## Experience

Safaricom PLC Software Developer May 2018 - Present Nairobi, Kenya

Part of the team implementing microservices & containerisation at the organisation using technologies such as Docker, Kubernetes and Java Spring among others.

Andela Software Developer June 2017 - Present Nairobi, Kenya

Andela provides companies with access to the top 1% of global tech talent. We identify high-potential developers on the African continent, shape them into world-class technical leaders, and pair them with companies as full-time, distributed team members. This allows Andela's partners, which range from startups to Fortune 500s, to accelerate their product roadmaps while minimizing time spent interviewing, on-boarding, and training new hires.

Andela is backed by investors including Spark Capital, Omidyar Network, Susa Ventures, Steve Case, Founder Collective, Rothenberg Ventures, Learn Capital and more.

Learn more about us at www.andela.com.

The National Treasury Intern May 2016 - July 2016 (3 months) Nairobi, Kenya

As an Information Technology intern at The National Treasury I was able to learn a lot about Information Technology as I assisted users resolve all their technological issues.

NairobiNet Online Intern May 2015 - June 2015 (2 months) Nairobi, Kenya

### Education

Multimedia University of Kenya
Bachelor's Degree, Information Technology · (2013 - 2017)